
// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is Katrina's Favorite Bread?",
    answer: "Croissant",   
    options: [
        "Croissant",
        "Sourdough",
        "Pineapple Bread",
        "Pita"   
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is Kat's Favorite Clothing Brand as of May 2022?",
    answer: "Theory",    
    options: [
    "COS",
    "Theory",
    "Oak+Fort",
    "Uniqlo"
       ]
  },

    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What instrument does Kat play (well lol)?", 
    answer: "flute",
    options: [
    "piano",
    "violin",
    "recorder",
    "flute"
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What Is Kat's Favorite Music Genre?",
    answer: "Jpop",
    options: [
        "Kpop",
        "Jpop",
        "Metal",
        "Indie"
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What is Kat's go-to Boba Order?",
    answer: "Yakult Green Tea",
    options: [ 
    "Classic Bubble Tea",
    "Brown Sugar Milk",
    "Strawberry Green Tea with Lychee Jelly",
    "Yakult Green Tea"
    ]
  },
  
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What is Kat's go-to restaurant in Chinatown NYC?",
    answer: "Spring Cafe on Canal Street",    
    options: [
    "Go Go Dim Sum",
    "The Original Bodai Restaurant",
    "Spring Cafe on Canal Street",
    "Happy Veggie Restaurant"
    ]
    },

    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Kat's favorite dish?",
    answer: "All Of The Above",
    options: [
    "Pasta (ANY TYPE)", 
    "Ramen", 
    "Mandy's Salad with Sesame Dressing", 
    "All Of The Above"
    ]
    },

    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Kat's Favorite Ghibli Animation Film",
    answer: "Howl's Moving Castle",
    options: [
    "Spirited Away", 
    "Ponyo", 
    "Howl's Moving Castle", 
    "Castle in the Sky"
    ]
    },
    
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "How Many Languages Does Kat Know Fluently",
    answer: "4",
    options: [
    "3", 
    "4", 
    "5", 
    "2"
    ]
    },

    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What is Kat's Chinese Zodiac Sign",
    answer: "Tiger",
    options: [
    "Rabbit", 
    "Tiger", 
    "Ox", 
    "Dragon"
    ]
    },

    {
    numb: 11,
    question: "What is Kat's Spirit Animal",
    answer: "Koala",
    options: [
    "Dolphin", 
    "Cheeta", 
    "Koala", 
    "Blobfish"
    ]
    }

];


